<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manoj Billa</title>
    <link>https://billa.rbind.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Manoj Billa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Manoj</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://billa.rbind.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://billa.rbind.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billa.rbind.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About I am a data enthusiast, interested in Descriptive and Predictive Analytics, Process &amp;amp; Supply Chain Optimization, Machine learning and Data Visualization. With a bachelors in Civil Engineering and a strong Math background, I chose to pursue my Masters in Information Systems at the University of Cincinnati to develop my Technical and Business skills. I started exploring data science field here and acquired many skills via the data Analytics certificate program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up my website</title>
      <link>https://billa.rbind.io/2018/12/11/setting-up-my-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billa.rbind.io/2018/12/11/setting-up-my-new-website/</guid>
      <description>FInally, after much deliberation, I finished building my new website. I Initially had a basic google sites website showcasing my projects, experience, etc. Then after experimenting with Jekyll, Ghost, Hugo, etc., I finally settled upon Hugo 😄. Then I discovered blogdown and moved my website into that. Yihui has written a pretty comprehensive book on blogdown which is available for free online and you should read that book if you want in-depth understanding of blogdown and hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old website</title>
      <link>https://billa.rbind.io/2016/10/10/old-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billa.rbind.io/2016/10/10/old-website/</guid>
      <description>Vist manojbilla.com to see some of my old work This site was built using google pages Link!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My awesome project</title>
      <link>https://billa.rbind.io/project/my-awesome-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billa.rbind.io/project/my-awesome-project/</guid>
      <description>About project Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>