<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Manoj Billa</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Manoj Billa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Manoj</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Udacity Python for Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/2019/05/15/udacity-python-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/05/15/udacity-python-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>These are my notes from the Udacity Python Course which I did as part of the Bertelsmann data science scholarship. This course covers basic Python and several Data Analysis packages of Python.
Python Basics  Python is case sensitive Variables can&amp;rsquo;t start with a number. They can&amp;rsquo;t have space. You can&amp;rsquo;t use reserved words like False, continue, if, etc too. Method behaves like a function but the methods are called using a dot notation There are two types of errors:Exceptions, Syntax</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Udacity SQL for Data Analysis using PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>/2019/04/20/udacity-sql-for-data-analysis-using-postgresql/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/20/udacity-sql-for-data-analysis-using-postgresql/</guid>
      <description>Last year, I got into the Bertelsmann data science scholarship where, along with Python, Statistics, I also got to brush up my SQL skills. Time and again, I see myself searching for SQL cheatsheets whenever I forget something. So I decided to write all the tricks and tips into a blog for easy reference.
Basic SQL Entity Relationship Diagram (ER Diagram) shows how data is structured and related in a database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up my website</title>
      <link>/2018/12/11/setting-up-my-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/11/setting-up-my-new-website/</guid>
      <description>FInally, after much deliberation, I finished building my new website. I Initially had a basic google sites website showcasing my projects, experience, etc. Then after experimenting with Jekyll, Ghost, Hugo, etc., I finally settled upon Hugo 😄. Then I discovered blogdown and moved my website into that. Yihui has written a pretty comprehensive book on blogdown which is available for free online and you should read that book if you want in-depth understanding of blogdown and hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old website</title>
      <link>/2016/10/10/old-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/10/old-website/</guid>
      <description>Vist manojbilla.com to see some of my old work This site was built using google pages!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>